allotment.org.uk 2016-11-25

# Your Privacy - Allotment & Gardens

Allotment & Gardens is managed by WebOneUK Ltd.

### General

This privacy policy explains what information WebOneUK Limited who manage the Allotment Garden web sites under the domains allotment.org.uk, allotment.org, allotment-garden.org etc collects and what that information is used for. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy please contact us via the contact page for Allotment Garden

### What information is used by WebOneUK Ltd for Allotment Garden?

We use the personal data, which you have provided, to supply you with the information, reference material, regulations, notes, guidelines or advice, which you have requested. The information and personal data is only collected and used for the purpose(s) for which it was provided. It is never sold or shared with any third parties except as defined in **Use and disclosure of personal information** below.

Your details are collected when you complete forms, request reference material, regulations, notes, guidelines or advice, or when you send us an email. We also use cookies and aggregate information.

### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small amount of information recording details of your visit to our web site but which does not identify you. The cookie is created by our web server and is saved on your PC’s hard drive. The next time you visit our web site, the web server will check to see if you have a cookie. If you have, the web server will be able to check the last time you visited the site.

If you do not want to receive cookies or, if you would prefer to be prompted first, you should check the settings in the “Internet Options” of your web browser. If you are not sure how to check or alter these settings, you should contact your software provider or support line.

Please be aware that disabling cookies will have a detrimental effect on your ability to contribute to the forums and to utilise some other facilities on the site.

### What is aggregate information?

Aggregate information is used to show us the total number of visits to our web site and which part(s) of the site are used most. Aggregate information does not identify individuals, as it does not contain personal data. The information helps us to develop our web site and improve the service it provides to you.

### Use and disclosure of personal information

Your information and personal data is not disclosed, sold or shared with any other organisations or persons outside WebOneUK Limited except where required by law with the following exceptions:

Some information is held and processed by our Internet service provider (ISP) but it is only held and processed for and on our behalf and under our instruction.

Information provided on the forums, such as email addresses, are available to administrators and moderators of the forum who are volunteers and not associated with WebOneUK Limited.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Allotment Garden is a participant in the Amazon EU Associates Programme, an affiliate advertising programme designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.co.uk

### Protection of personal information

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding use of your data you can contact us via the contact page
